I think it's very hard.
Everyone, all 12 of us, including Kishi.
I'm more flabbergasted than I thought I would be.
We're all in a hurry.
Aaah! Ouch!
Farewell, Farewell, Hapiola, you're all one!
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
Please. Good morning.
Good morning Good morning Good morning
Always the best stage Welcome
Pasta Promise
My favorite lunch corner.
It's 11:15.
Yes, sir.
The noon show starts at 1:00 p.m.
I'm so nervous... this is my 7th show... but at lunchtime...
I get a stomach ache every time I hear we're about to leave.
I'm so nervous.
It's more chaotic than I thought, everyone's in a hurry.
We don't have much time left.
We're all running out of time, we're all running out of time.
Hirao.
There's a message here.
Hirao Sono-chan!
It's been a while since we've had a daytime/nighttime performance.
I'm so nervous.
Starting from the 7th show.
"Tokimitsuo" will be performed at the 7th show.Tokimitsuo was going to be in the show.
We've only had about 3 hours each for the choreography and the set.
I'm a little nervous because we're going to perform it right off the bat.
I'll do my best.
Are you a little nervous?
Everyone's a little flustered.
We didn't have much time.
So let's get into it.
We need to tighten it up.
Let's do it again.
Okay. - Okay.
Here we go.
For the seventh show, will you put your heart and soul into it?
Will you be the loudest you've ever been?
Here we go!
Violet.
Hello!
Kahorin!
Mitsuki.
Tamaki
Kiraho
Anishi
Yaka
Kira
Kirali
Rio
Monaka
Until then, Happy Hello Unity!
Hee.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Today's Theatre Milanza Opening Series
Thank you for coming to the Live Art Theatre Milanza in Shinzanmon.
Thank you very much.
Before we begin, we would like to make a few requests and announcements
Please do not bring cameras, video cameras, binoculars with recording functions, or any other recording devices into the venue.
Please refrain from bringing or using cameras, video cameras, recording binoculars, and other recording equipment into the venue.
Cameras may be present for video recording and photography.
Please be aware that you may be filmed
Please understand this in advance.
Please wait for a while until the show starts.
Sun, can you speak up as loud as you can?
Don't let Smilida's voice get the better of you!
Congratulations!
U schon
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you for your hard work
Next time preview
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your hard work.
It was a lot of fun.
I know that you are probably tired,
I hope you have a good rest and finish the remaining 3 shows safely.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for coming to the show today.
I hope that I can be closer to my seniors and continue to follow their backs, We hope that we can follow the backs of our seniors so that we can become even closer to them,
I will continue to devote myself to further improvement of the 4th group.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
It's a little boring.
Yes, from the second place, why?
Really?
3rd grade?
I can run fast.
I'm happy with second place.
That's great.
Everyone was smiling and doing their best even when we were in 2nd place and a half,
I guess it was a tough time for everyone,
I was a little worried because some of the kids cried when I brought them some food,
But the children's voices were a big part of the show, and it was a very hot show.
Real Curve
Oh, there were too many people!
Good morning!
From now on
People, people, wait
Thank you
Rina
Yes, sir.
Rina-chan, wait for another one.
Oh, poo.
Thank you very much.
Spitcher.
Thank you.
Yay.Yay!
Ria.
Yes, I did.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, sorry for the extra baggage.
Eee...
Will you do something for me?
Christmas.
First.
LOL.
Hey.
I'm gonna cry. I'm gonna cry.
Just right.
The wind is chillin'.
I'm so touched that everyone is looking in the mirror right now and smiling and doing their best.
Thank you so much for letting us play our song!
Go for it! You guys will be fine!
You guys are really doing your best to keep it up.
The MCs and the dads were giving it their all.
Tadayoshi-sama can feel it.
I think it would be hard if we did this every day.
but everyone, all 12 of us including Kishi-kun
Please whisper when you die and do your best!
Hang in there! I was thinking...
Thank you for your hard work!
In Itougetsuki
I would like to insert INTERFERENCE
Kan ka ληη shika!
list
What color is this? What color is this?
Color ice
It's not in a few colors.
Kapi
What time is it? 30 seconds.
Do you have any water?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, I'm gonna die.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's for the night.
Oh, my God!
This is a real surprise.
What? individuals
Reaction
Oh, but it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
No way.
That's how it's supposed to be.
I want you to go out in front of the audience
I don't want to be in the front
I don't like it.
What's wrong with you?
We're rehearsing for the full show.
We just finished the full show.
We just finished the full performance.
But now we're going to start rehearsing for the live streaming of the show.
We're going to do our best to prepare for the camera and the streaming.
Yuta, everyone who's watching the streaming, please do this for us.
I'll be Yuruko!
I'm going to be Yuruko!
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best!I'll do my best.
Good night.
Rehearsal's over.
I'm hungry.
I know you're hungry.
Have you eaten?
No.
I hope we have time.
I'm in such a state.
Oh, here it comes.
Too much beef?
I'll take it from India before the show.
You have to eat.
Thank you.
I don't have time.
I'm writing.
This lunch is really good.
I want to eat it slowly.
It's really good!
I have to go.
No, you don't.
You're busy.
Two and a half minutes to go.
It's been too long.
I don't know.
I'm just...
I've become a person who squirms a lot.
I'm so hungry
Anyway, I'mAnyway, I'm
I'm really
I'm hungry.
Hungry
A stack of tires
Just a little
Take it off
Take it off.
Where am I supposed to be nervous?
Let's do it at the beginning! Come on!
Come on, Tamaki! Come on!
Please.
I'm begging you.
Today, I'm going to make this the hottest live in Japan with Kagere, so let's really make it the hottest live in Japan.
Let's make it the hottest show in Japan.
Then, we can do it all.
Let's show them everything we can do in the 4th term.
The 12 of us can do it.
All of it, all of it.
Are you ready?
I'm in.
We made the 8th show the hottest live in Japan!
Huh!
Yes! Let's go! Can you jump high? Yes!Yes! Here we go! Can you jump high? Yes!
Here we go! Ha-ha! No car! Hitzki! Kamesh! Killary! Rizzer! Samakee! Kalkaa! Milaha! Milah! Milah! Manakar!
Survive! Surprise! Happy! Yoller! Oneness! Bee!
Thank you!
Thank you very much for coming to the opening series of Theater Minanoza, New Gate Live Art Theater Minanoza today!
Before we begin, we would like to make a few requests and announcements
Please refrain from bringing in and using video cameras, recording devices, binoculars, and other filming and recording equipment in the venue.
Smoking and eating are prohibited in the auditorium.
Please eat, drink and smoke in the designated areas.
Please wait for a while until the show starts.
Are you ready to get excited?
Let's make this the hottest show in Japan!
Ho, MT, wading in!
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 49, 50, 51. 52, 53, 54, 56, 57, 59, 60, 61, 62, 61, 62, 62, 63, 62, 63, 62, 63, 63, 64, 67, 61, 6 1, 62, 61, 62, 61, 61, 61, 61, 61, 61, 61, 61, 61, 61
SOU
We, the fourth term students, have decided to put everything we have into this newcomer!
This Shinza thing is really the last chance for the 4th term students
We have performed at one school and one school at a time with great care.
We hope that you will continue to walk with us for a long time to come.
We, the 4th term students...
We will never forget our original intention
We'll keep on pushing forward with all our might.
We will keep going forward with all our might.
Thank you very much for coming today.
We, Shikisei, will continue to climb many walls in the future.
I hope you will watch over us.
That's all for us
Hinanozaka46 Shikisei.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much
me
Thank you for a great time!
Thank you!
Thank you for all the good times!
Please come see me again!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
First show is over.
Just after.
It was so much fun, and I was so happy to hear the applause and people saying how good it was until the very end.
I was so happy to hear people applauding and saying how good it was until the very end!
It was really great.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
I had a lot of regrets about the first show.
I managed to change my mind a little bit and reflect on it.
I was able to give it my all for the 8th show!
Who's that?
Rio!
How did you know?
We're all here together.
Cool.
It's cool. "cool
Cool!
I was really nervous and anxious today.
But I'm so glad that I was able to make it to the night show
I'm so glad that we were able to welcome the audience to the evening performance.
We'll make sure you won't miss it!
Please watch us give it our all!
Please watch us!